BEN KALSKY

UX DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Experienced Product Owner with a demonstrated history of working in the interactive media industry.

Skilled in UX principles and UI design methods. Strong arts and design professional graduated from Avni Institute of Art and Design.

CONTACT

ADDRESS

Azor, Israel

PHONE

+972-528816959

EMAIL

benkalsky@gmail.com

WEBSITE

http://benkalsky.com

HOBBY

Coffee, Beatch, Photography, Traveling the World and eating great food :)

EXPERIENCE

2007-2018 **Freelance**

UX Developer & Consultant

2017-2018 **Dome9 Security**

UX Engineer

2014-2017 **Apester**

Creative Director

EDUCATION

2010-2014 Avni Institute of Art &

Design

Interactive Media Design

2002-2005 Israel Defense Forces

Professional Photography

1996-2002 Boyer High School

Biology & Music

SKILLS

UX, UI, Prototyping, Interaction, Web, Graphic Design, Typography, Web Development, Branding & Identity, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Angular.js, WordPress, Photography, After Effects, Vector Illustration, jQuery, JavaScript, Start-ups, Entrepreneurship